(Leonard:)What do we do?
Should we call someone?
(Howard:)And tell them that we
compromised all the equipment?
(Howard:)Let's just get it out of
here before anyone knows.
(Leonard:)Okay, how do we catch it?
(Howard:)Well, what if we turn
off all the lights
(Howard:)except for one, and
it'll come to it.
It's not a moth!
(Howard:)Don't yell at me.
(Howard:)You're not gonna get
any good ideas out of me
(Howard:)if you're yelling.
(Leonard:)Okay, so if I remain calm,
(Leonard:)I'll get more gems like,
"Turn off the lights"?!
(Howard:)Great, we're turning
on each other.
(Howard:)That's just what the
bird wants us to do!
(Penny:)So, Dr. Koothrappali,
long flight?
20 hours.
Oh, that's rough.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Not at all. Did you know that
when you fly transcontinental
(Dr Koothrappali:)without your wife, you don't
pray for the plane to crash?
Can you please talk
about anything else?
(Dr Koothrappali:)Forgive me.
(Dr Koothrappali:)How are you
and Leonard?
(Penny:)Oh, great.
Everything's good.
(Dr Koothrappali:)I see you got engaged.
Yes, we did.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Let me tell you a story.